JASON KIM

SUWANEE, GA 30024 | 404.694.9923 | youngmin13@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/jasondotkim/ | github.com/eccentricality https://jsonkimify.tech

SUMMARY

Full Stack Web Developer, trained professional with 10 years of learning experiences within industries ranging from grassroots, to legal, to financial institutions; bringing unparalleled levels of soft skills and professionalism, coupled with intelligence and analytics. Highly technical by nature and a team player, successful on numerous occasions in a team environment collaborating across diverse groups both as a leader and a teammate; for example, my times as a civic engagement associate as well as teammate for Bootcamp projects. Eager candidate looking to bring these experiences to add immense values as well as learn and continuously adapt in a collaborative environment.

PROJECTS

Movie Information Search | Repository | https://eccentricality.github.io/hollywoodHackers/

Users can search for their favorite movies to obtain fun facts about them and actors with little snippets about them.

- Role in Project: JavaScript for first group project.
- Technologies Used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, OMDB API, IMDB API, NY TIMES API.

Weather Search | Repository | https://eccentricality.github.io/weatherSearch/

Allows users to search for a 5 day forecast.

- Role in Project: Self-developed for Bootcamp project.
- Technologies Used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Open Weather API.

Daily Scheduler | Repository | https://eccentricality.github.io/workDay/

Allows users to locally store daily to-do items in each time slot by the hour.

- Role in Project: Self-developed for Bootcamp project.
- Technologies Used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Moment.js.

Code Quiz | Repository | https://eccentricality.github.io/codeQuiz/

Timed quiz that allows users to locally store high scores.

- Role in Project: Self-developed for Bootcamp project.
- Technologies Used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript.

Interactive Rock Paper Scissors | Repository | https://eccentricality.github.io/RPS/

Interactive game where a computer player randomly generates a throw and in response to the user's throw.

- Role in Project: Self-developed for practice and enjoyment.
- Technologies Used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript.

Password Generator | Repository | https://eccentricality.github.io/pwGenerator/

Generates between 8 - 128 characters with options to include lower case, upper case, numbers as well as symbols.

- Role in Project: Self-developed for Bootcamp project.
- Technologies Used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

LANGUAGES: HTML, CSS, JavaScript **OTHER:** GitHub, Microsoft Office Suite

EXPERIENCE

Bank of America, Suwanee, GA (February 2021 - Present)

Paycheck Protection Program Tier 2 Triage

- Worked on a team of 10 members remotely in a work from home environment.
- Demonstrated highly effective customer service skills with ability to manage the full client end-to-end experience and problem resolution.
- Processed 5+ client files per day following internal regulation guidelines and principles.

Merrill Lynch, Pierce, Fenner & Smith, Inc., Atlanta, GA (January 2020 - February 2021) Financial Advisor Trainee

- Involved in a national program with a local team of 50 or so professionally trained members.
- Studied for and passed the Securities Industry Essentials exam and the Series 7 exam, one full month ahead of schedule compared to fellow cohort members.
- Supported CARES Paycheck Protection Program origination.

Alex Tortoso Agency, Fort Oglethorpe, GA (April 2019 - January 2020)

Insurance Broker

- Worked with a team of 2 other members in a small office environment.
- Attended various networking events to promote the business in a self-run business model.
- Provided thorough analysis about various nuances of insurance coverage to prospects.

Paul Slavik State Farm Agency, Roswell, GA (October 2017 - April 2019)

Sales Agent Aspirant

- Worked with a team of 2 other members and a few interns in a small office environment.
- Conducted training sessions for staff members on how to perform phone calls and in person sales meetings.
- Attended various networking events to promote the business in a self-run business model.

Asian Americans Advancing Justice — Atlanta, Norcross, GA (August 2014 - February 2015)

Civic Engagement Associate

- Worked with a local team of 3 other members and on occasions nationally with teams from other regions ranging from 5 to 10 members for national level efforts to draw attention.
- Conducted research and analysis on the President's executive order for DACA/DAPA services.
- Coordinated and executed door to door canvassing and phone banking for 20+ volunteers.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Developer Bootcamp Certificate

Georgia Institute of Technology, Atlanta, GA (October 2021)

Juris Doctor

Atlanta's John Marshall Law School, Atlanta, GA (May 2013)

Bachelor of Arts / English

SUNY Binghamton University, Binghamton, NY (May 2008)